{
    "id": "edb16059f63a4c40a417701f6c8c2035",
    "title": "If, Otherwise, Unless",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We must hurry up .................................. we will miss the train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "otherwise",
                "if",
                "unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "73a7088a8fe942b393f0679d43af03eb"
        },
        {
            "question": "....................................... we do not hurry up, we will miss the train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Otherwise"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2b41c8b18bde44e4888ed4ee70345222"
        },
        {
            "question": "......................................... we hurry up, we will miss the train.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Otherwise"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f03cc94623fc49ef96afbe7c5c3caada"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must work hard ....................................., you will fail the test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "if",
                "otherwise"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6dbbc154b49f4d06a1b901c6588a9dce"
        },
        {
            "question": "........................................... you do not work hard, you will fail the test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Unless",
                "Otherwise",
                "If"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "28127364bcc84655bc2d9b410886d5db"
        },
        {
            "question": "...................................... you work hard, you will fail the test.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Unless",
                "If",
                "Otherwise"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5db3ca5383b6463e8f6bf94a4c6a8313"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are in love with him. Why do you want to pretend .......................................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "unless",
                "otherwise"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a7b8fc6a68ca434c90635f88e77952f4"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hope she mends her ways. ........................................., she will be sacked.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Otherwise"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "75e14fc571af4c4baeb73244b394d8c1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The vaccine has saved tens of thousands of children who would ................................... have died.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "Unless",
                "otherwise"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "278c1e02cb1d42b5a4dfe5e680a31535"
        },
        {
            "question": "Of course she is interested in him. ............................................., she wouldnâ€™t be asking about his whereabouts.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "Unless",
                "Otherwise"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0e12c9cdf40b493aab992adac49e75c2"
        }
    ]
}